bookrenter.com 2006-06-17

# BookRenter.com ::

To better guard your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. 

**Our Commitment**   
We are completely committed to keeping your personal identity safe. The information you provide is used to process orders and to assist in providing you with a more personalized shopping experience. In addition, we may monitor customer traffic patterns and site usage to help us develop the content, design, and layout of a better overall site. Please refer to the Secure Site Policy page to find out all the technical measures we use to keep you identity protected. 

**Information We Collect**   
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on BookRenter.com. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected there are: 

  * Name 
  * Shipping Address 
  * Billing Address 
  * Email Address 
  * Phone Number 
  * Credit/Debit Card Information 
  * School Information 

On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you want an order sent to someone other than yourself, you will need to submit the recipient's personal information. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected are: 
  * Name 
  * Shipping Address 
  * Phone Number 
  * School Information 

**The Way We Use Your Information**   
When you place an order, we use your personal information to process and fulfill your order and to notify you of your order status. Occasionally, we may use your email address to deliver information regarding important changes to our website, new services, and special offers that might be of interest. If you would rather not receive this type of information, please visit the Mailing List Page to manage your subscriptions. 

We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purposes and are not shared with any third parties. 

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out. 

**How to Access/Correct Your Information**   
You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect and maintain by clicking on the My Account section. We safeguard this procedure by only allowing password granted access. 

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by making updates to this section. In the event of accessing your personal information outside of the My Account section, to protect your privacy you must provide three of the following identifiers: email, password, home phone number, and/or address to verify your identity before making corrections. 

**Cookies**   
"Cookies" are small bits of information stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive to store your settings and remember the contents of your shopping cart as you navigate through BookRenter.com. However, our cookies do not contain any personal information. Most web browsers automatically default to accept cookies. If you desire not to accept cookies, you can modify your internet browser's settings. 

**Disclosure to Third Parties**  
Your personal information is after all yours and we do not sell, trade, or rent any of it without your permission. If you do not want us to share your personal information with trusted third parties, you can uncheck that option when sending us your information. If you ever change your mind in the future, you can always opt out by changing your preferences in the My Account section. 

BookRenter.com may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns and related site information to reputable third parties that we collaborate or engage in business with. However, these statistics will include no personal information. 

BookRenter.com releases personal account information, in good faith, when such release is believed to be logically necessary. This includes situations to comply with the law, enforce or apply the terms of any of our user agreements, and protect the rights, property and safety of BookRenter.com, our customers, and affected third parties. 

**Unsubscribing from Our email List**  
You may choose not to receive any additional email communications. BookRenter.com completely respects this right and if you only wish to receive basic communications regarding your order status and tracking, you can visit our Mailing List Page to do so. 

**Your Password**  
BookRenter.com suggests that you keep your password private and avoid disclosing it to any third parties. If others have access to your password, the possibility exists that your personal information could be accessed and compromised. 

**Changes**  
By using BookRenter.com, you consent to our collection and use of this information. If we amend our Privacy Policy, we will post the changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we gather, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. We suggest that you check this page on occasion to keep up with our most current policies.
